exterminate-it.com 2011-06-09

# Exterminate It!: Privacy Policy

###### Top 10 Alerts

###### Latest 10 malware files

###### Testimonials

Hey Matt,  
It worked! You guys are INCREDIBLE!! I cannot thank you enough. Best money I ever spent on a piece of software. My entire LIFE was on my PC and if it wasn't for Exterminate It! and the help from you, well to be blunt, I would of just been screwed! I pray that you guys will keep doin what your doin. This is not the first time I've had trouble with my pc and am sure it wont be my last. Every time I've ended up reformatting and losing everything, BUT NOT THIS TIME!! WOOHOO!! I will tell EVERYONE about your software and will be a customer for life!

THANK YOU AGAIN!!! 

Erik R.

More ...

###### Latest Blog Posts

## General

This Privacy Policy applies to CurioLab’s Exterminate It! web site (further referred to as “Site”) and Exterminate It! software (further referred to as “Software”).

This policy may change from time to time so it is recommended that you check it regularly. All updates will be published on this site.

As a company that is committed to protecting your privacy, we understand your desire to safeguard your personal information. Whenever you provide us with your personal data, you give your consent to collect and use it in accordance with our privacy policy. We will not share any of your personal information with any third parties, unless required by law, without your permission.

## Exterminate It! Web Site

The Site does not use “cookies” to store your information during online sessions. When and if we add cookies in the future, we will modify this statement accordingly.

Information that is collected through the Site is the information that you explicitly provide using the Feedback and Support pages.

The Site includes a number of links to our business partners, with whom we have a variety of relationships. CurioLab is not responsible for the privacy practices of these business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements as they may differ from ours.

## Online Payment Processing

The ordering process is secure since the orders are processed by RegNow.com, an industry leader in providing e-commerce processing and online credit card processing services.

We do not store any credit card information; we collect only your personal information such as your name and email address. We use this information to supply the activation information to you.

Credit card processing is performed solely by RegNow.com—never by Exterminate It! itself.

## Exterminate It! Software

The Software does not send any private information to the Site.

Only the following information is sent to the Site:

  * Activation code generated during the activation process
  * A list of malware found during a virus scanning process (sent for statistical purposes)
  * A system snapshot during the uninstall process (sent for detection improving purposes)
  * A system snapshot when the “Submit State” feature was used   
Please note that a system snapshot includes NO private information.

We do not disclose your e-mail address to business partners or to anyone other than our employees. CurioLab may contact you by e-mail to respond to comments, feedback, and customer service inquiries you submitted.

We send e-mails using the following addresses: 

  * @exterminate-it.com
  * @curiolab.net

If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, please contact us at [privacy@exterminate-it.com](mailto:privacy@exterminate-it.com).

CURIOLAB S.M.B.A., Amagertorv 15, 2, 1160 Copenhagen K, Denmark, +45.36965533
